No, this is definitely good information.
I don't want to have a super housing loan.
What is your scheme?
There is no answer in the bank of Maharashtra.
So, I can tell the manager that this is your scheme.
I don't want to have a super housing loan.
I don't want that.
Or, if someone thinks that my loan is under some scheme,
then they won't get the information.
If the customer doesn't know, then they will get the information.
Any other information?
It is very important.
There is a scheme under the name of Maharashtra Bank of Maharashtra.
Any other information?
Just think about a better way to show the money.
This is the best way.
But, the draw points are good.
But, this is the static information.
How do other banks do it?
They put a page in each of the other banks.
We will talk about that page.
But, not as a blog.
It is an information.
But, it should be out there.
It should be in the product.
More details.
It is good.
It is not important.
But, it should be in the product.
It should be in the same product.
The bank of Maharashtra didn't underline it.
They put a clip in it.
Then, it got blocked.
I am told that there is more important information.
But, I am told that it is the same information.
It is not important information.
I am told that you should see this too.
ADD.info
It should not be big.
It should not be on the phone.
Column should not be big.
You have to put the plus sign.
How to guess underline?
There is something.
If you put it on a loan amount, it will give you more calculations.
It will give you more calculations.
If you put it under the bank of Maharashtra, it will give you more calculations.
It should not be a big deal.
I think it is important information.
This is the dump of all information.
It is clickable.
It is the same.
Generally, when people are told what is inside, they click it.
Click it.
If you want to know more about it, click it.
If you want to know more about the bank of Maharashtra, click it.
But if you take the super housing loan, I think you should know more about the loan.
If you take the super housing loan, you will get to know more about it.
It is a little misleading.
I think it is important information.
It is not important information.
It is not standard.
Earlier, we used to write a solenoid.
We used to write more details.
It is more and more.
If you write something, it is more.
What is this?
This is the thing.
It is good.
It is definitely good.
You just have to follow 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
What is this?
You took 48 lakhs.
You took 55,000.
What is this?
You didn't take it.
This information is great.
You took credit card.
If you took credit card, it would have been 10 lakhs.
And then 1 lakh.
Then 1 lakh.
Okay.
We calculate and calculate the loan amount.
And the interest is lowered.
2.40 months.
Where is 2.40 months?
20 years.
This is 9 months.
Yes, this is 20 years.
This is my eligibility.
I have to pay 14,000.
But what about this?
I don't know.
It's not just neat.
If you have a color code, it will show you.
Look, bro.
Minimum of 2.
Then left-side calculation, right-side calculation.
1-2-3, 1-2-3.
Minimum of 2.
Yes.
Yes, it's correct.
Minimum of 2.
Okay.
20%
Yes, it's directly.
That's the limit.
Yes, that's the limit.
Yes, then keep this much.
And the second one is this.
First, this is 25.
Then this is 1 lakh.
And the third one is this.
This is 1 lakh.